(Beverley:)What do you think?
(Penny:)Well, we are known
for our cheesecake.
(Penny:)-Hit us again.
-Yes.
(Beverley:)-If a little is good, more must be better.
-Ha, ha.
(Penny:)-Hey, Bev, guess what?
-What?
(Penny:)I'm sleeping with your son.
(Penny:)Really?
(Beverley:)Which one?
(Penny:)The one from whom
I live across the hall from.
Oh, well, that's convenient.
How did his penis turn out?
(Penny:)Oh, Beverly, I can't talk to
my boyfriend's mother about his penis.
(Beverley:)Oh, fair enough.
(Beverley:)What can you tell me, if anything,
about that busboy's penis?
(Penny:)Actually, I've only had the cheesecake.
(Penny:)One more time.
You know, Leonard did not wanna
tell you we were dating.